phporder.com 2012-05-25

# Purium Health Products | Offering Whole Food Nutrition & Organic Supplements for Holistic Health

**Overview**   
Purium Health Products recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information we collect from you. Purium is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information. 

**Purpose**  
This Policy explains how Purium collects, uses, stores and discloses information, including personal information. Purium is committed to collecting, using, storing and disclosing personal information responsibly. By using Purium’s websites, you consent to the collection of personal information. Information that is provided will only be used, stored and disclosed for the purposes for which you have consented. 

**Purium’s Collection and Use Of Information**   
Purium collects personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, email and telephone numbers entered on our websites or provided directly to Purium Health Products. Purium uses such information for all legal purposes and to provide products and services to you. Purium may use and disclose the personal information we collect about you in order to: 

  * Process your transactions 
  * Create and manage your accounts 
  * Process Applications 
  * Notify you about product order status 
  * Develop downline genealogy reports 
  * Provide Member and Distributor services and administer benefits 
  * Send information about Purium events and product specials 
  * Develop and implement policies, marketing plans, and strategies 
  * Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests 
  * Comply with applicable laws and regulatory requirements 
  * Enforce our Terms and Conditions and otherwise manage our business 

Security  
We are committed to keeping personal information secure. This website has security measures to help protect against loss, misuse and alteration of sensitive information such as credit card and social security numbers. Purium uses security measures consistent with standard industry practice to protect that information. 

**Information Sharing**   
Purium is not in the business of selling customer personal information to third parties. Purium may share such information from time to time as described below. 

Third Party Service Providers: We use third party service providers to help us operate our business or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending emails, fulfilling your product and service requests, mailing products or managing payments. We may share your information with these third parties for limited purposes. 

Purium Independent Distributors: Purchases of Purium products through our websites are credited to a Purium Independent Distributor, who is available to provide service, information and/or guidance in taking advantage of the benefits of membership in Purium. Information you provide to us will also be provided to the Purium Independent Distributor to whom your purchase has been assigned in order to facilitate that experience. 

If you are a Purium Independent Distributor, we may disclose certain personal information such as your contact information to customers seeking a Purium Independent Distributor or to other Purium Independent Distributors such as your upline Business Leader. 

Other Disclosures: We may disclose your personal information where required or permitted by law or to protect and defend the rights of Purium Health Products. 

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this Policy or the practices of this website, you may contact the Purium Customer Service Department using the “Support” button on this site.
